Senate Democrats are currently debating this idea of whether to place conditions on the funding.
One of the arguments in favor is that Congress does this for nearly every other country that it gives foreign military assistance to.
What is your response to that?
I think it's ridiculous.
Our relationship with Israel is the closest national security relationship we have with any country in the world.
And to condition, in effect, our assistance to Israel on their meeting our standards, it seems to me, is totally unnecessary.
This is a democracy, a great ally of ours, and I do not think we need to condition the support that hopefully we'll give to Israel very soon.
Okay, so maybe you're like, I mean, I don't care about if Israel is holding Palestinians in an apartheid regime.
Like, I just don't care about none of that.
Maybe you care about the fact that when America is giving all this money to Israel, they are able to do things with it that America says it cannot do for Americans.
They have universal health care.
They have free college.
They have housing.
Like, these are things that America says we don't have the power, but yet we're giving money to a country that is able to implement that to its own citizens.
That should bother you.